Junk food is now a staple of many Americans’ diets.
如今，垃圾食品已是许多美国人日常饮食中的主要部分。
Advertising campaigns from the snack food companies, often featuring sports stars, send the message that we can neutralize any negative effects of consuming their products simply by getting more physical exercise.
零食公司的广告宣传常常请体育明星出镜，传递这样一个信息：只要多做体育锻炼，我们就能抵消食用其产品带来的任何负面影响。
But recent studies show a lack of exercise is not to blame for rising obesity rates.
但近期的研究表明，肥胖率上升并不能归咎于缺乏锻炼。
Bad diets are.
该怪的是不良饮食。
Interventions to help reduce junk food consumption are especially important for children and teenagers.
帮助减少垃圾食品摄入的干预措施对儿童和青少年尤其重要。
Prevention is better than cure because obesity is so difficult to treat.
预防胜于治疗，因为肥胖非常难以治疗。
Unfortunately, while health education has shown some success among young children, teens have been harder to reach.
遗憾的是，虽然健康教育在幼儿身上取得了一些成效，但对青少年却一直更难奏效。
Now a large-scale study has tried an innovative approach to change teenagers’ attitudes towards healthy eating, and the results are promising.
如今，一项大规模研究尝试用一种创新方法来改变青少年对健康饮食的态度，结果令人鼓舞。
The researchers argued that previous interventions have probably been unsuccessful because of a major flaw: they focused on a future, healthier you and assumed that this would be enough motivation for teenagers.
研究人员认为，以往的干预措施很可能是因为一个重大缺陷而没有成功：它们着眼于未来那个更健康的自己，并以为这足以激励青少年。
In contrast, the new intervention cleverly exploits teenagers’ instinct for rebelliousness and autonomy, and the value they place on social justice.
相比之下，新的干预措施巧妙地利用了青少年叛逆和追求自主的天性，以及他们对社会公正的重视。
To do this, researchers had students read an article on the food industry.
为此，研究人员让学生阅读了一篇关于食品行业的文章。
It revealed a secret about the manipulative and deceptive strategies used to make junk food more addictive and characterize the products as healthy.
文章揭露了一个秘密：为了让垃圾食品更容易使人上瘾，并把这类产品标榜为健康食品，食品行业采用了操纵性和欺骗性的策略。
The article also explained how advertising campaigns specifically target very young and poor people, causing harm to these vulnerable groups.
文章还说明了广告宣传如何专门瞄准低龄儿童和穷人，给这些弱势群体造成伤害。
Afterwards, the participants read a fictional survey of teens who wanted to “fight back against the companies by buying and eating less processed food.”
随后，参与者阅读了一份虚构的调查，调查对象是一些想要“通过少买、少吃加工食品来反击这些公司”的青少年。
After the intervention, participants associated healthy eating with autonomy and social justice.
干预之后，参与者把健康饮食与自主和社会公正联系在了一起。
The teenagers also rated healthy eating as being more appealing.
这些青少年对健康饮食吸引力的评价也更高了。
Importantly, there were also some promising effects of the new intervention on actual behavior.
重要的是，新的干预措施对实际行为也产生了一些令人鼓舞的效果。
A day later the students were offered a choice of snacks and drinks in a seemingly unrelated context.
一天后，研究人员在一个看似毫不相关的情境中，让学生们从一些零食和饮料中挑选。
The teens more often chose healthy snacks and drinks (such as fruit or water) over unhealthy options (like biscuits and soda).
这些青少年更常选择健康的零食和饮料（如水果或水），而不是不健康的选项（如饼干和汽水）。
Associating a healthy diet with teenagers’ own values seems to be a promising avenue to prevent obesity.
把健康饮食与青少年自身的价值观联系起来，似乎是预防肥胖的一条有前景的途径。